[Music] daddy and ward curry udon not much time
[音乐]爸爸和沃德咖喱乌冬面时间不多
war on a class with journey to find of gun in my universe
在我的宇宙中寻找枪支的旅程上上课
the first or we only have a site by for not too big for other
第一个，或者我们只有一个网站，对于其他网站来说，该网站不能太大
for this silent method you got it one million euros insider
对于这种无声的方法，您可以获得一百万欧元的内幕消息
map music on the sangha people were to be helped the size of a pencil eraser
僧伽人的地图音乐将得到帮助，就像橡皮擦一样大
you planet play soccer some one side scream and me so any other
你的星球踢足球，一边尖叫，我一边踢足球
the pointwood and cities chats the sun mixes my the nine point nine process or
我的九点九程序或我的点材和城市聊天太阳混合或
album as in the entire solar system girls basically hot stuff for mother
像整个太阳系中的专辑一样，女孩基本上是妈妈的热门东西
Santing is made from and the what you can take for stars shine I see you the mill
Santing是由它制成，您可以拿走些许星星，我看到您的磨坊
mary nestor the figure and becomes hardcore
玛丽·内斯特（mary nestor）成为人物
this doctors chain of chemical reactions hydrogen arms kids with a twitch separate
这个医生的化学反应链氢用抽搐分开给孩子们武器
form helium releasing in a credible amount or
形成大量释放的氦气或
energy pads the store slide not as bigger stars as legal brother because we
能量垫商店滑动不像合法兄弟那样大，因为我们
with cars responses king to the showroom historically lifespan earnings arts
从历史上看，汽车是国王对陈列室的回应
stormed enter the giant face angle expert and torn red
冲进巨人脸角专家并撕成红色
hood springs effective testament the big star wolf ai is likely to be on the edge
胡德·斯普林斯的有效遗嘱大明星沃尔夫·艾可能会处于边缘
of its life [Music]
一生[音乐]
switching anarchy perlite engines we should arrive at lumens 16 system
切换无政府状态的珍珠岩引擎，我们应该到达流明16系统
here hoofs from the narrow stars and they're all round wolf
这里是狭窄恒星的蹄子，它们都是狼
small here whose and that the size you bridge what disturb smolov
小这里的人和你的大小桥接什么打扰斯莫洛夫
brown village as well as roodveld star's edge of heaven of mass produced chemical
棕色村庄以及Roodveld星的大规模生产化学物质的天堂边缘
reactions that monster know this bright what
怪物知道这个聪明的反应是什么
super des hauts the modern aspects gather so tightly
现代的超级集会紧密地聚集在一起
dw details more than you there have been same size and if i think that something
dw的详细信息要比您多，而且尺寸相同，如果我认为
just look at all right or i the murder highly tackles
只是看好吧，否则我的谋杀案就可以解决
this one here is sirius b something also bought the size of super league smudges
这是天狼星b东西，也买了超级联赛污点的大小
bison mix in this with dim white light once it
野牛一旦混入，它就会发出暗淡的白光
branch arya's resource to rescue and cooldown
阿里亚支行的资源进行救援和降温
nightfly closer to the giant neighbor sirius b
靠近巨大邻居西里乌斯b的夜蛾
you can easily see the starting mars hotels merchants
您可以轻松地看到火星酒店的首批商人
twice here and murders men have times wider than our sun kids have the bridal
在这里两次，谋杀者比我们的太阳孩子拥有新娘更宽广的时代
store in online sky nou we fly 500 if the lie you so why
如果您撒谎，我们会在网上储存500天的诺诺飞行，为什么呢？
killed by the constellation kassiopi you to us a hundred years ago a cosmic
一百年前你被我们的卡西奥皮星座杀死了
explosion here here i spinned that atmosphere existed gaming kassiopi je and
在这里爆炸，我旋转说存在气氛存在游戏卡西奥皮耶和
sunglasses became ronan the space after there hippique in prehistoric times and
太阳镜在史前时代嬉皮之后成为罗南（ronan）的空间，
the constellation a little over times wider than our son on to
这个星座比我们的儿子宽了几倍
the famous noordstar funny and off the free starship agile over the years and
多年来，著名的noordstar很有趣，而且免费的星际飞船敏捷，并且
more will take it in future test picosearch polestar
更多信息将在以后的测试中使用picosearch polestar
changes every tony's x 1000 niers imagine art planet leaks spinning top
改变每一个托尼的x 1000个尼尔斯，想象艺术星球泄漏自上而下
the north pole was shift around in another circle
北极又转了一圈
pony you that prince torsten the throne or santa claus is a super giant store the
小马，你说王子把宝座或圣诞老人折成超级大商店了
seven times wider and 5 times heavier than our son
比我们儿子宽7倍，重5倍
this easy define the night sky hits at the verichip
这很容易定义verichip的夜空
on the lidl dippers lever get ready no more sharing or pda you go to the store
在Lidl铲斗杆上准备好了，不再需要共享或pda了，您去商店了
there hot milky white galaxy the see the nextorch jun the switch too
那里有热的乳白色银河系，也可以看到nextorch jun
infograph mode this gun store is hiding from as in
该枪支商店躲藏起来的信息图模式
space dust in just five seconds ditto it is much light sr home store die
太空尘埃仅需五秒钟就可以照亮sr家庭商店的死亡
in one and theory you slightly aysist char dropping
在一个理论上，你稍微不认同char下降
the track 100 ronnie times wider than the sun when it's still not the most
当它不是最强时，轨道比太阳宽100 ronnie倍
luminous star need i manage walibi applause super giant in the
发光的星星需要我管理瓦利比掌声中的超级巨人
constellation triangle does not fit it before one size
星座三角形不适合一个尺寸
most and million times brighter than the sun
比太阳亮最多一百万倍
that the wider star fell the fast returns up everything and the short ribs live
较宽的恒星下降，快速返回一切，而短肋骨活着
computer with a red dwarf the pearly close and brings you much more slowly
带有红色小矮星的计算机，珍珠般的关闭，让您走得更慢
that's life of pi one hundred or a thousand and time sure there for the four hundred
那就是pi的生命一百或一千，时间肯定在那里四百
live earth earth mother ethel estilo buddies and universe
活着的地球地球母亲ethel estilo伙伴和宇宙
this them your ipod giant potro kassiopi your tonsils can restore mustache galaxy
这是您的ipod巨型potro kassiopi您的扁桃体可以还原胡子星系
de romea couple thousands of base and i will do the stars extremely far away
de romea夫妇有成千上万的基地，我将在遥远的地方做星星
from artline it you can still see the sky with old no
从artline上，您仍然可以看到天空，没有旧的
things telescope that speaker sets 300,000 times rider the
扬声器设置30万次骑行者的事物望远镜
narsigh in also helps that thing is mine
narsigh也可以帮助我解决这个问题
mother times wider than argon start your and is color tellson's pads users will
母亲比氩气大的倍数会开始您的使用，而彩色泰森的护垫使用者会
last for a long time monro kasia ps doctors rescue and expert
持续了很长时间monro kasia ps医生救援和专家
in obi-wan the peaks stores in the entire universe
ob湾的山峰遍布整个宇宙
well we must be the constellation ryan the story ar sites beetlejuice
好吧，我们一定要成为这个故事的基地ryan的地盘ryan
months larger ones visible to the a no die seven hundred times the sidebar sun
几个月大的肉眼看不到侧杆太阳的700倍
you this pulled her starsplash this service must touch diaz call back
你这拉她的星星，这项服务必须碰到diaz回调
that between your bets on jupiter and mars you become in gulf de for inner planets
在您对木星和火星的赌注之间，您将陷入内部行星的鸿沟
yard and toddler what is thor he his straw numbers four ix-ai the pepper dik pieltjes
院子里的小孩他的稻草是什么，四号ix-ai胡椒粉dik pieltjes
will explode in a fantastic celestial show in an extendas meurs
将在延伸的梦幻般的天体表演中爆炸
i will be the greatest ask took some went off all time this will be able to
我将是最大的要求，要花一些时间，这将能够
return false supernova are close with 7 of distance that explosion
返回虚假超新星与爆炸距离7接近
star line is bry de them you will be visible in the details guide
星线是bry de他们，您将在详细信息指南中看到
for here and the night process from or no adventure to stars that I see the
在这里和从无冒险到无恒星的夜晚过程中，我看到了
songs with one thousand eyes news fbi is a hyperjuice posting the tidal other
一千眼的歌曲新闻FBI是一种潮水般的潮汐式传播。
eddystone star kids color gel so that the fugee's coming closer and closer the mc
eddystone star kids彩色gel喱，让fugee越来越靠近mc
where the silent sobek pedigree already gold billion suns in it
无声的索贝克血统书中已经有十亿日圆的太阳
and because of its mesh the starworld angeles the common supernova pore of
由于其网状结构，星际天使拥有了共同的超新星孔隙
a black hole let's take it ripple most for home and
一个黑洞让我们把它带回家的最深处
likers van han here is a red super giant kaldeway
范汉（Van Han）一样，是一个红色的超级巨人卡尔德威
meet george this is where the beasts turned stars on the milky way i wit it
遇见乔治，这是野兽在银河系中变星的地方
3 billion suns and here the never so cute this thing is like that
30亿个太阳，这里从来没有像现在这样可爱过
pricing relight ponies 17 which on site in context or celestia buddies
在现场或天才好友现场定价的小马17
you could call this store in a flash the reward in the next one harder bag and
您可以在下一个较硬的购物袋中迅速致电这家商店以作为奖励
conquer who mike ines measures will explode one
征服迈克·伊内斯的措施将爆炸
hype er nova chemoradiation will destroy all live in the loco horses the universe
炒作新星化学辐射将摧毁宇宙中所有活着的疯子
what is thor is so for marshall there system we put him in and around your axis
对于马歇尔来说，这是什么，那里有系统，我们把他放进了你的轴心
every place and live via in the center for solar system
每个地方都生活在太阳能系统的中心
this must be polder model too boring resorted to remind you just how far away saturn
这一定是田模式太无聊了，以至于提醒你土星有多远
I think it's why it takes the sun slide 1 minute streeters
我认为这就是为什么需要花1分钟的时间让太阳滑行道的人
the get together it does take over a hr computer this mess up store
在一起，它确实需要一台HR计算机，这家杂乱无章的商店
the sun is so the green or cm kids live most luminous and rest
太阳是绿色的，所以绿色或厘米级的孩子最容易发光和休息
stars and ar universe the bigger and red the star is the carbonation
恒星和ar宇宙越大，红色越多，恒星是碳化
twitch en zo Hoorn looking adjust the time of the
twitch en zo Hoorn寻找调整时间
universe we also one of the oldest celestia baris altair
宇宙，我们也是最古老的天神巴里斯·阿尔泰尔之一
the second biggest star universe is you wiseguy
第二大恒星宇宙是你明智
isabel onecoin 5 trillion miles white 16 times the distance from the gates the
伊莎贝尔onecoin 5万亿英里白色距离大门的距离是16倍
sun this is the wrist earring variable star kids brightness changes every two years
太阳这是手腕耳环变星，孩子的亮度每两年改变一次
the wise guy is heading there in feel compost interior
聪明的家伙正走向堆肥内部
scientist expected to wall pack to leak harder temperatures yolo join our
科学家希望壁挂能够泄漏更严酷的温度yolo加入我们的行列
journey is coming to with the force how to birol stevenson 2nd team
旅程即将到来如何让史蒂文森第二队
it doesn't take to be a track like here from historic reacher
不需要像以前的足迹一样走这条路
this kind of wet CDs red super giant anartha not restaurant
这种湿的CD红色超级巨人anartha不是餐厅
this is 2100 if the times wider than our site would meet and billion suns too much
如果比我们站点宽的时间会遇到并且十亿个太阳过多，则为2100
something podium for commerce and the average page contains only about 5
讲台上的商务和平均页面仅包含约5
trillion grains or cm
万亿谷物或厘米